<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Gregg(awatt)</title>
    <link>https://greggawatt.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Gregg(awatt)</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2022 20:58:47 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://greggawatt.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Doomscrolling and The Spectacle</title>
      <link>https://greggawatt.github.io/posts/doomscrolling-and-the-spectacle/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2022 20:58:47 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://greggawatt.github.io/posts/doomscrolling-and-the-spectacle/</guid>
      <description>About a month ago, I deleted twitter.
Twitter was a useful tool for me since 2007, I was a very early user of the platform and remember when you could text to it to post. I saw value in the platform early on for decentralized communications. I build software to help activists use the platform and used it myself during the oscar grant rebellions, occupy oakland and many more.
I have met many people who I still really enjoy on Twitter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to contact the ISS with a Baofeng</title>
      <link>https://greggawatt.github.io/posts/contact-the-iss-baofeng/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Dec 2020 10:14:08 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://greggawatt.github.io/posts/contact-the-iss-baofeng/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been a bit obsessed with trying to talk to space lately
Did you know the International Space Station has a ham radio repeater? I&amp;rsquo;ve known this for years but now that I&amp;rsquo;m in the world of ham radio, I can do something about it.
First off you should know what I&amp;rsquo;m working with:
Baofeng UV-5R 4w Ed Fong Dual Band DBJ-1 Why would you want to do this? Well the repeater can allow you to get contacts to people in areas outside of your normal range with just VHF/UHF, also beaming to space is fun.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Talks And Workshops</title>
      <link>https://greggawatt.github.io/talks/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Dec 2020 08:57:50 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://greggawatt.github.io/talks/</guid>
      <description>2021 March PancakesCon 2
Threat Modeling and How To Contact the ISS with a 30 dollar radio
2020 August DefCon: App Sec Village
10,000 dependencies under the sea: Exploring and Securing Open Source Dependencies
2014 July Hope X
Surveillance, Sousveillance, and Anti-Surveillance: Artistic Responses to Watching</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
